silversnowball.com 2011-11-24

# PRIVACY POLICY

PRIVACY POLICY

SILVERSNOWBALL.COM strives to offer its visitors the many  
advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive  
and personalized experience. We may use Personally Identifiable  
Information (your name, e-mail address, street address,  
telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy.  
Please be assured we will never sell, barter, or rent your  
email address to any unauthorized third party.

How We Gather Information From Users

How we collect and store information depends on the page you  
are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate  
and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to  
provide information when you register for access to certain  
portions of our site or request certain features, such as more  
information, newsletters or when you make a purchase. You may  
provide information when you participate in sweepstakes and  
contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other interactive  
areas of our site. Like most Web sites, SILVERSNOWBALL.COM  
also collects information automatically and through the use of  
electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For  
example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider  
or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information  
from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your  
user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter  
that information each time you visit, or may control the number  
of times you encounter a particular advertisement while  
visiting our site. As we adopt additional technology, we may  
also gather information through other means. In certain cases,  
you can choose not to provide us with information, for example  
by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you  
do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or  
may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we  
may not be able to customize the site's features according to  
your preferences.

Website visitors who wish to communicate with the website do so  
under two conditions:  one, they give their permission for  
contact by the website; two, they are subject to any submission   
provisions of the Terms of Use, Purchase Agreement, or this   
Privacy Policy.  

What We Do With The Information We Collect

Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance  
your visit and deliver more individualized content and  
advertising. We respect your privacy and do not share your  
information with anyone.

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally  
identify you) may be used in many ways. For example, we may  
combine information about your usage patterns with similar  
information obtained from other users to help enhance our site  
and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or  
what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may  
occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business  
partners. Again, this information does not include any  
Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone  
to identify you individually.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on  
SILVERSNOWBALL.COM to communicate with you about your  
registration and customization preferences; our Terms of  
Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by  
SILVERSNOWBALL.COM and other topics we think you might find of  
interest.

Personally Identifiable Information collected by  
SILVERSNOWBALL.COM may also be used for other purposes,  
including but not limited to site administration,  
troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions,  
administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other  
communications with you. Certain third parties who provide  
technical support for the operation of our site (our Web  
hosting service for example) may access such information. We  
will use your information only as permitted by law. In  
addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our  
business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other  
companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information  
may be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your  
information in response to a court order, at other times when  
we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in  
connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us,  
and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it  
appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you  
with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

INFORMATION THAT IS NOT SHARED

Credit card information or other financial information is not  
usually known to the website.  However, in the event that it is  
made known, that information is never revealed to anyone except  
to processing authorities or law enforcement agencies.  
However, the provider of such information gives express  
permission to use it in fraud investigation or for litigation.

CUSTOMER EMAIL OR TESTIMONIALS

If you are a customer and send an email to the website, or if  
you communicate with the site by phone or mail, the website  
collects information about your communication.  By  
communicating with the site you give your permission to  
collect, archive, retrieve, and otherwise use any information  
collected as the site sees fit.

Any communication which, in its sole discretion, the site deems  
to be a testimonial, may be publicized for commercial purposes.

Affiliated Sites, Linked Sites And Advertisements

SILVERSNOWBALL.COM expects its partners, advertisers and  
affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware,  
however, that third parties, including our partners,  
advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible  
through our site, may have their own privacy and data  
collection policies and practices. For example, during your  
visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame  
on a SILVERSNOWBALL.COM page, certain content that is actually  
created or hosted by a third party. Also, through  
SILVERSNOWBALL.COM you may be introduced to, or be able to  
access, information, Web sites, features, contests or  
sweepstakes offered by other parties. SILVERSNOWBALL.COM is not  
responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties.  
You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third  
parties when providing information on a feature or page  
operated by a third party.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose  
Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in  
chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be  
collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and  
may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or  
third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of  
SILVERSNOWBALL.COM and this policy.

While we take measures to ensure that outside parties do not  
have access to any information we have about you, we do not  
warranty that outside parties will not breach our system and  
thus have access to your information. 

PERSONS UNDER 18 YEARS OF AGE ARE EXCLUDED  
FROM THIS WEBSITE

This website is not lawfully accessible to persons under the  
age of 18 or who are otherwise covered by the provisions of the  
Child Online Privacy Act of 1998 (COPA).  If you are under the  
age of 18 you must leave this site immediately.  Fraudulent use  
of this website may make you subject to civil or criminal  
sanctions.

VIEWING AND/OR USE AND/OR COMMUNICATION IS   
CONSTRUED AS ACCEPTANCE OF THE TERMS OF THIS POLICY

Contacting Us

We can be reached by contacting: EMAIL:  silversnowball @  
silversnowball.com

Changes to this Policy

SILVERSNOWBALL.COM reserves the right to change this policy at  
any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your  
continued use of our site following the posting of changes to  
these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information  
collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used  
according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the  
information was collected.

Latest Update

This Privacy Policy was last updated on: April, 2008

Governing law

This policy and the use of this Site are governed by Massachusetts  
law. If a dispute arises under this Policy we agree to  
first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed-upon  
mediator in the following location: United States, Massachusetts.  
Any costs and fees other than attorney fees associated  
with the mediation will be shared equally by each of us.

If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory  
solution through mediation, we agree to submit the dispute to  
binding arbitration at the following location: United States),  
Massachusetts., under the rules of the American Arbitration  
Association. Judgment upon the award rendered by the  
arbitration may be entered in any court with jurisdiction to do  
so.

SILVERSNOWBALL.COM is controlled, operated and administered  
entirely within Massachusetts. This statement and the  
policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create  
any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any

party.
